YD.
Do you know what it is?
Yukata Dating?
Yakiniku Desires?
Wrong!
You Do only what you want.
That's me, Kagami Junichirou!
Keep your car out of my way.
That's enough.
...we could do it with a game.
You want to settle this with a game?
I'll just have to leak all sorts of shameful pictures of your precious Kanou-senpai on the internet.
Wait, what!?
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true!
ichido no jinsei yaritai koto yaranakya
You only get one life so you gotta do the things you want
iza to nattara mucha shite omoshorikushite yarouze
So when it comes down to it, just shake things up and have some crazy fun
tsumaranai koto suru kimi ni wa oshioki ga hitsuyou kana?
But you never have any fun, do you need a little motivation?
seken no joushiki nanka wa kowashite
Set out to destroy society's preconceptions
kagami ni utsuru itsumono hyoujou kaeteyaruze
We'll swap that sour look for the one reflected in the mirror
soshite ichido suicchi iretara hoshii mono wa te ni irero
Once you flip your switch, your dreams will come within reach
hiiroo ga inakereba kimi ga hiiroo ni nareba ii to
"If there's no such thing as heroes, then you'll just have to become one."
sonna kotoba ga ikiru imi wo ataete kureta (donna shougai mo koete yuku)
Your words gave meaning to my life (I can overcome any obstacle)
kimaru no wa jibun nano
You choose the path you take
demo ne hitoribocchi ja nai kara
But that doesn't mean you need to walk it alone
monogatari no kotoba de ima sugu hontou no hiiroo ni nare!
Live up to the story you told me, become a true hero!
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true
kimi no ayumu jinsei orijinaru na sonzai sa
No matter what path you choose, it'll be your own original story
reberu agete tobidase mada mita koto no nai keshiki ga matsu
Level up and take to the skies, there's so much you've yet to see
kira kira to kagayakeru rejendo rea na bijon de egakareta
Like in your radiant vision of a sparkling legend
saikou no suteeji wo mezase!
you have to aim for the highest stage!
You!
What's with this underhanded crap!?
Why don't you meet my team?
One of the top four teams in the prefectural tournament,
Icho Academy's soccer club!
Yeah!
And here's your team.
The Higashi Shinmei High School's girls' soccer club.
Let's have a good game!
Wh-What the hell is this!?
Let's have a nice, fair game!
You!
In what way is this nice and fair?
This is so unfair.
Well then,
let's begin the game.
He is an Ultimate
Otaku Teacher
#06
SEARCH
An Interesting Sight
Then I, Hiiragi Koyomi, shall be the referee.
I'm fine with that.
But Lovely Options,
do you even know the rules of soccer?
I have read every volume of Our Field.
In that case, you'll be fine!
Really?
Before we begin, a reminder.
The winner will take the rights to the loser's life.
Kagami Junichirou vs Nanami Seijuurou.
Let the soccer showdown commence!
Hey, Sensei...
Are you sure that thing you mentioned earlier will be fine?
Yeah, just leave it to me.
You'll get it right after the game.
Something he mentioned earlier?
Bribery, huh?
Why else would our soccer club
cooperate with an otaku teacher?
I see how it is.
If that's how you wanna play,
I guess I will too.
Begin the game!
Take this!
Big brother!
Serves you right, Otaku Teacher!
Wait a minute, referee!
Shouldn't he be red carded for that!?
Nice tackle!
Does she really know the rules?
Goal!
Kagami team!
Team Kagami Team Nanami
Yay!
That's a point for us!
I'm looking forward to having you as my slave.
Over here!
I have no idea what you're up to,
but you won't be grinning like that for long—
Goal!
And there's our second goal.
You're...
such an easy character to read.
You!
Nanami-kun!
I have no idea what you're yelling about,
but would you please play the game properly?
We're here to play a real game of soccer.
I don't want to lose!
Damn it!
Even if you ask me to play properly,
I don't even know how to dribble the ball!
Goal!
Yay!
Hey! There's the third!
You!
Nanami-kun!
Shut up!
Let's stop here!
That concludes the first half.
It's halftime.
Here, big brother.
Oh, thank you.
If you can keep up this pace, you'll win for sure.
Nanami-kun?
I've had enough of this already! I quit!
I can't put up with this!
There's no way this girls' team can defeat our school's soccer club.
Or rather, why the hell did I let that dirty otaku teacher
talk me into this soccer game in the first place!?
I'm such an idiot.
Nanami-kun!
I'm glad someone's finally making this interesting.
Now...
let the lesson begin!
Moreover, there were many political reforms and the capital was moved from Asuka to Naniwa.
They built the palace in a place called Toyosakinomiya.
Kagami Junichirou has sent you a message.
From Kagami-sensei?
The years from then on brought immensely famous...
Sender: Kagami Junichirou
Address: Kanou Minako
Subject: No Subject
Seijuurou's giving up on the game.
Sender: Kagami Junichirou
Address: Kanou Minako
Subject: No Subject
Seijuurou's giving up on the game.
Huh?
What do you want?
If you're worried about the slave thing,
we could just settle it here with our fists.
There's no need.
What need do I have for a slave who's as obedient as you?
You agreed to a showdown,
only to back out when things weren't looking so good for you.
What a wise decision that was.
You should be grateful for being raised so well...
by your papa.
You!
The second half of the match is about to start.
Listen up, all of you!
I'm staying in the game after all.
I'll get it this time...
Here.
Goal!
Sensei, are you sure about this?
We feel like the bad guys right now.
Don't worry about that.
This is where it gets interesting.
We're ready for your transformation,
Cyborg!
It's no use, they're too strong.
If this continues...
...they'll beat us!
In both power and speed...
The girls are just no match for these guys.
And I can't even dribble properly.
Damn it, what am I supposed to do?
Seijuurou!
What do you think you're doing, playing normal soccer?
Have you already forgotten your training!?
S-Senpai?
Oh, support character, perfect timing!
That's it!
Trust me...
with the rest of the match.
I'm gonna turn this thing around.
Pass.
Okay!
The girls' team is starting to make successful passes.
They stopped trying to make more risky forward passes.
But if you're just passing your ball around your defense line
you can't really score any goals.
Did they give up on winning?
Well, I wouldn't blame them.
That was a rather long kick
and nobody's even running towards it.
Must have been a miskick—
Protect the goal!
It's not like they cou—
Goal!
Finally!
Wh-What!?
What just happened!?
The long ball play...
A tactic where you kick a long ball from your own half of the field to the opponents penalty area.
It's only possible for a very strong and powerful striker.
It's one of the strongest tactics in video game soccer.
Video game soccer?
But in order for it to be successful in reality,
you would need a forward who can run as fast as the ball.
You'd think someone like that would only exist in a video game,
but he has the inhuman strength needed to pull it off.
Yay!
I did it!
As expected of the Cyborg, Nanami Seijuurou!
His potential never got by me!
Team Kagami Team Nanami
Goal!
Amazing!
Five points...
They caught up just like that and tied the game.
Are you serious?
They stole five goals from us in the blink of an eye.
All they're doing is blasting those long balls through us.
That's the terrifying part of the long ball play.
Sensei?
Not only is it simple, it's unstoppable.
That's why it's a tactic that's
prohibited in multiplayer matches.
But that's just video game talk!
There's no way that pass is unblockable in real life.
Listen up! There's not much time left!
Let's counterattack now!
Don't let the ball through!
Okay!
It's the other way around.
The long ball tactic requires legs that can run as fast as the ball
and the ability to overpower the
opponents goalkeepers and defenders.
He's coming!
Everyone, get ready!
Think about this:
what would happen if there was a human with the ability
to make a serious attempt at the long ball play?
Not even a video game character would be able to stop him.
And for that reason, a human player wouldn't ever stand a chance.
Goal!
He did it!
The match has ended!
With a score of six to five, Nanami's team stands victorious!
We did it!
All right!
He was defeated.
My big brother's gonna be a slave forever...
Yo!
Time to fulfill your promise.
You're my slave from this day forward,
Otaku Teacher.
Oh,
you're right...
Hold on, prick!
It's too late to tell me it was all a joke. What's with that smirk of yours!?
Nanami-kun!
You were fantastic!
To beat the boys' team, it's like we're dreaming!
Thank you, Nanami-kun!
"With Nanami-kun on your team,
you'll win against even the boys."
Kagami-sensei was right!
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Just the other day, Sensei asked us to help you in a soccer match.
He said he would tell the school it was a friendly match to get permission.
Wait, that girl?
She was the one sitting with Sensei at the café.
You'll see!
In two days from now, you'll see some of the hottest goals in the world!
Oh, is that true?
Yeah, you bet!
He was...
Well, it's already clear who's gonna win—
What do you think you're doing, Sensei!?
He must have been talking about Nanami-kun.
Well, what's the meaning of this?
Nanami!
You're amazing!
You brought your team back from being five points down. That's nuts!
I've never seen someone play soccer like that.
Wh-What?
As expected of our team's new ace.
Your...
new ace?
What?
What? No one told you?
Sensei promised to introduce us to a forward as powerful as a video game character
if we played a match with him.
It sounded too good to be true.
I couldn't take him seriously at first,
but he stood outside my house all night, not budging an inch.
Eventually, I gave in.
Come to think of it...
I hope he explodes!
Huh, what?
Just what are you up to, big brother!?
So that was the reason...
That explains why big brother didn't come home that night.
Agreeing to play was definitely the right choice.
I agree, Captain!
We'll definitely make it to the nationals this year!
Anyway,
we've been searching for a forward like you for a long time!
These guys want to play soccer with you.
Why don't you join them?
But I've never played soccer.
That's not a problem!
With your physique,
you'll get the hang of it in no time.
Looking forward to playing with you.
Playing with you is boring.
Why don't you just play alone?
However, that way of life will only lead to loneliness.
You're no longer alone.
Did big brother put on this soccer match just to get Nanami back on his feet?
Of course not.
He reminded me of a needy animal from a farming sim game!
You've still got a few kinks and flaws as a cyborg,
but with my hands, those can be hammered out.
This was such a thrilling modification project!
You!
I'm not your toy!
Besides, once you've achieved perfection...
I'll get to see the most interesting thing in my life.
That's all there is to it.
You'll see something interesting?
Watching you was just like watching a video game character come to life.
That was so cool to see!
Was that really all he wanted?
That person will probably be a real idiot.
However, that way of life will only lead to loneliness.
And you'll come to regret your entire life.
But in spite of that, you can still
overcome it all and change yourself.
Some day, undoubtedly...
you will find a friend that will stand next to you,
looking towards the same future.
However, that person...
will probably be a huge idiot.
According to him, the only reason he made me play soccer
was to watch something interesting...
I guess I've lost,
Otaku Teacher.
Wait, what?
I believe we agreed the loser would be the winner's slave.
I'll do whatever you say.
Do what you want with me.
Stay just the way you are.
Hey!
That's the end of today's lesson.
Seijuurou!
Senpai?
You were so incredible!
"You Do only what you want."
So that's YD, huh?
He did win Senpai's heart, after all.
What a great guy.
Wh-What are you saying!?
Senpai, stop!
That was impressive.
This time, I handled this exactly how you planned.
Well, then? Did you find that interesting?
Yes, very.
I'll show you what happens when you're full of yourself!
Just as I thought. Inviting you to our school was the right choice.
Have a taste of my sleeper hold, Seijuurou!
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
hibikasetai
I want it to resound,
kono koe o habatakasete
carry my voice,
sekaijuu ni furu na ai wo (aiou)
and fill the world with love
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell everyone that they can't stop dreamin'
shingou ga kawaru to sugu ni
As the signals change
hito no nami nagasaresou de
I get swept away in the crowd
kono machi wo aruku ni wa kitto
To walk the streets of this town
burenai kokoro hitsuyou
you need an unshakable heart
biru no sukima no kyuukutsu na sora ni
In that strip of sky between the city highrises
hikouki ga kirameita
I saw the sparkle of a plane fly by
watashi mo isoganakucha
I'd better get going, too
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
mou matenai
I just can't wait any more!
ooki na kaze maki okoshite
I'll raise a great wind
saidaifuusoku de ai wo (aiou)
and reach max speed so I can give you my love!
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell you that you can't stop dreamin'
Next Episode
SEARCH
This is big brother's little sister, Kagami Suzune.
It was a lot of work, but Nanami's our friend now.
I'm sure we'll all stay good friends!
In the next episode...
We meet the most beautiful girl at our school, Chinami Kanon.
She only speaks to us through text messages.
No one's ever heard her voice.
Seventh Lecture: A Beautiful Girl's Secret.
Rumor has it she sounds like an anime character.
Ah, hold it big brother! Don't make her say weird stuff!