YD.
Do you know what it is?
Yukata Dating?
Yakiniku Desires?
Wrong!
You Do only what you want.
That's me, Kagami Junichirou!
Help! A molester!
This has spread all over the internet.
Sensei, please don't resign!
Sensei, I—
Don't ever think that abiding by the rules will guarantee your usefulness to society.
Refine your weapon!
Force reality to accept your rules!
If you can manage that, the future is all yours.
yume o kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true!
ichido no jinsei yaritai koto yaranakya
You only get one life so you gotta do the things you want
iza to nattara mucha shite omoshirokushite yarouze
So when it comes down to it, just shake things up and have some crazy fun
tsumaranai koto suru kimi ni wa oshioki ga hitsuyou kana?
But you never have any fun, do you need a little motivation?
seken no joushiki nanka wa kowashite
Set out to destroy society's preconceptions
kagami ni utsuru itsumono hyoujou kaeteyaruze
We'll swap that sour look for the one reflected in the mirror
soshite ichido suicchi iretara hoshii mono wa te ni irero
Once you flip your switch, your dreams will come within reach
hiiroo ga inakereba kimi ga hiiroo ni nareba ii to
"If there's no such thing as heroes, then you'll just have to become one."
sonna kotoba ga ikiru imi wo ataete kureta (donna shougai mo koete yuku)
Your words gave meaning to my life (I can overcome any obstacle)
kimeru no wa jibun nano
You choose the path you take
demo ne hitoribocchi ja nai kara
But that doesn't mean you need to walk it alone
monogatari no kotoba de ima sugu hontou no hiiroo ni nare!
Live up to the story you told me, become a true hero!
yume o kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true
kimi no ayumu jinsei | orijinaru na sonzai sa
No matter what path you choose, it'll be your own original story
reberu agete tobidase mada mita koto no nai keshiki ga matsu
Level up and take to the skies, there's so much you've yet to see
kirakira to kagayakeru rejendo rea na bijon de egakareta
Like in your radiant vision of a sparkling legend
saikou no suteeji wo mezase!
you have to aim for the highest stage!
I happen to be Hiiragi Private Academy's board chairwoman,
Hiiragi Koyomi.
I am here to hire you...
Kagami Junichirou-sensei.
Hire me?
Yes.
There has been quite a bit of commotion recently
in regards to your brilliant teaching at Higashi Shinmei High School.
I received word that you were for some reason being dismissed by this school,
so I decided an immediate visit was in order.
W-Well...
I know exactly what you're thinking right now.
You're wondering why such a lovely girl is the chairwoman of a school.
Not even close!
I'm not speaking to you today as a beautiful girl,
but as a previous chairwoman's grandchild,
who had many different options to choose from.
Options?
But why would you come all this way just to hire someone like me?
Elite teachers are a dime a dozen these days.
And let's not forget the fact that it's been a full five years
since all the commotion over my theory—
My, how naive you are.
Do you really believe I would show up to hire you personally
just because you had a theory published in Nature?
Kagami-sensei, I'm going to transform Japan.
In order for this country to continue to flourish,
I will plant the seeds of the future
via the education at my school.
What blooms will be nothing like this country's current economy or industry.
I have but a single vision...
An interesting country! Japan!
The reason I want to hire you is because I find you interesting...
Kagami Junichirou-sensei.
I'm expecting an agreeable answer from you,
so please consider my offer thoroughly.
I will be paying your home a visit tomorrow morning,
and I hope you'll have an answer to greet me with.
And with that...
An interesting country?
He is an Ultimate
Otaku Teacher
#03
SEARCH
Chase in Akihabara
Huh!? They want to hire you!?
Hiiragi Academy?
That's the school I go to.
Didn't you go to Icho Academy?
My school is a branch campus of Hiiragi Academy.
Does that make Hiiragi Academy some sort of super posh school?
What's with you?
That's the kind of face you'd give your parents when they find your BL stash.
Shut up!
Not that I know what that means!
Unlike the normal students who study at Icho Academy,
Hiiragi Academy only accepts students who are extremely talented.
That means the place is crawling with the craziest and scariest kids.
Icho students try to avoid the campus because of that.
I've even heard stories of students getting lost on Hiiragi's campus
and mysteriously disappearing!
Sounds like some kind of zombie film out of Hollywood.
Even the most qualified teachers have
trouble dealing with the students there.
They hired a teacher with a Nobel Prize not
too long ago who didn't even last three days.
I think I understand now.
I guess that means Lovely Options wasn't lying.
Lovely Options?
Isn't that great, though?
You don't need to go back to being a NEET now.
That's a weight off my shoulders.
Regarding that, I've already made up my mind.
This is my decision as the chairwoman.
Understood?
What should I do?
APRIL 2015
Crap! I don't have much time!
I'm really sorry!
I can't find him anywhere in the house.
He should understand how important today is...
I promise I'll find him! I'll drag him here if I have to!
Man, just what on earth is he thinking!?
He was so lucky to be offered this job!
That will not be necessary.
What?
We will simply find find him ourselves.
Once we've done that, we can ask him about it in person.
Uh... Chairwoman?
Well, let us be off!
I knew she was rich, but I didn't expect her to be the kind that would throw away common sense.
So, where are we heading?
Where are we going?
We are currently trying to locate Kagami-sensei.
The reports should come in momentarily.
Koyomi-sama,
Tango 2 is on the line. Repeat.
Tango 2, Yokoyama.
Our satellite has confirmed the location of our target.
S-Satellite?
The target is progressing towards the
Akihabara district in the Chiyoda ward.
Good work. Let us begin operation Crimson Flower at once.
Establish our Head Quarters on Chuo Street.
Furthermore, all units are to refrain from causing trouble to civilians.
Take all measures necessary.
E-Excuse me?
Do we really need to go this far?
Suzune-san... was it?
There is no need to worry.
We will find Kagami-sensei soon enough.
Akihabara...
What an interesting place to take refuge, Kagami-sensei.
Come. This way.
Please give me a minute!
We could just call him instead of going through all this trouble.
Hey, what's up, little sister?
Big brother? Where are you right now?
It's so noisy on your end!
What do you think you're doing!?
Head back home right now!
The chairwoman came to see you!
I think you're forgetting something.
Sure, she wanted to hire me,
but I never said I'd take the job.
You know, I have YD.
I'd rather stay cooped up at home than take another teaching job.
It suits me better, you could say. Sorry, little sister.
I have much more important
things to do than teach right now.
Later!
Seriously!?
It would seem your negotiations fell through.
I'm really sorry.
I will bring him back however possible!
Oh, hold on a moment.
Yes?
Take this.
If something should happen,
you are to contact me with this.
That number is a direct line to me.
Thank you.
Well, then...
She really cares about her brother...
Well then, I shall try my own methods as well.
I'm coming,
Kagami-sensei!
Yankee 1, Suwa, in position.
Tango 2, Yokoyama, in position.
Alpha 1, Iwata, in position.
All units are in position!
Commence operation White Flower Bud.
All units, begin operation White Flower Bud.
Confirm your target.
Target: Kagami Junichirou
Height: 175 Centimeters
Wearing glasses
Brown hair
Pink hoodie and white labcoat
Currently mobile in Akihabara.
Target: Kagami Junichirou.
Height: 175 Centimeters.
Currently wearing glasses. Has brown hair.
He is currently wearing a pink
hooded jacket, with a white lab coat.
He's currently mobile in Akihabara.
All units are to report visual contact immediately.
I repeat...
Engineering team, please track the target's cellphone and double check the surveillance camera feeds.
Report when necessary.
Akihabara is known as the Electric Town.
Its safety is secured by countless surveillance cameras.
Since we have the police department helping us,
pulling feeds from satellites and surveillance cameras is simple.
We even have the area sealed off.
NO ENTRY
In other words, not even an ant could slip by unnoticed.
I have even mobilized an army of around 200 detectives.
Let's see if I, Hiiragi Koyomi, will achieve victory, or if your abilities exceed even mine.
Show me what you're capable of,
Kagami-sensei.
Oscar 1, Azuma. The target, Kagami Junichirou, is in sight.
He is currently moving from area D3 to D6.
I'm in pursuit, awaiting orders.
Tango 3, Mizogami. Target is currently in front of Anumate.
He's entering the store.
Should we detain him?
Leave him be a little longer.
Pursue him into the store.
Whiskey 1, Maekawa. Target is exiting the store!
Oscar 1, Azuma. I'm sorry, I lost sight of the target in area D6!
I'm sorry to report that the target's knowledge of the area seems to surpass our own.
Well, I didn't rule this out as a possibility.
If capturing him proved to be that simple, this would be a dull task indeed.
We've lost the target's cellphone signal.
It would seem he has switched it off.
All units, his cellphone was last traced to area D6 before it was lost.
Patrol that area!
There he is!
Huh?
What is this?
Have you seen this person?
Oh, Kagami-san?
He was here just a moment ago.
I just missed him. Darn!
Yankee 1, Suwa. Someone fitting the target's profile has been spotted in the Oroden store.
The surveillance cameras in the store are unable to give us a visual.
Confirm that it's the target.
It's not him!
Yankee 2, Yonekura, in area E4. Target in sight.
Please come with us.
Sorry, you two, but I'm a little busy right now.
Then...
What!?
Target is on the run!
Yankee 2, Yonekura.
I'm sorry, contact was made with the target in area D6!
How should we proceed?
Our current strategy is reaching its limits.
It would be best if we moved in and secured the target at once.
I'm busy! My schedule is bursting at the seams.
I don't have time to keep you guys company!
Welcome back home, Master!
What the heck is up with those guys?
Lovely Options is in Akiba?
Don't tell me...
If that's the case, I should give them all I've got.
Yankee 3, Kikugawa, from area A4. Target in sight.
Can you confirm the target you've marked in A4?
Please verify.
What do you mean by that?
Currently, agents from all areas are reporting a visual of the target.
Tango 3, Mizogami, from area D3. Target in sight!
Tango 1, Yoshioka. Target in sight in area F1. He's in F1!
Just what I'd expect from you, Kagami-sensei.
You're pulling this off.
Man, where did he run off to?
He's going to want more french fries soon.
It's no use I guess...
Is that...
Engineering team, how is the face recognition system coming along?
Well...
The camera feeds are being swapped out with dummy videos!
What!?
I don't know all the details yet, but it's possible that...
He's hacking us!
Well, the first mistake you made was thinking you could possibly outsmart me in Akiba.
Just give up already!
Oh... Just in time.
He's breaking through our firewall!
The system's going... down.
An utter defeat.
I should have expected this from a man of your caliber,
Kagami-sensei.
Magical Girl
Bura     Kura
Voice Actress Autograph Event
To Kagami
Junichirou-san
From Sgt.
Thunders
Yes! I finally got it!
An autograph from Hanazono Kanon-chan,
the girl who voiced Sergeant Thunders—
Found you!
Kagami-sensei.
Let me go!
Stuffing me in a sack is inhumane!
But Suzune-san, how did you find this place?
We tried our best to catch him, but to no avail.
I'm shocked.
I went to all the usual spots my big brother visits,
and I came across this Magical Girl Bura-Kura signing event.
To Kagami
Junichirou-san
From Sgt.
Thunders
I just knew he'd be here.
In short, he's been frantically running around for a measly autograph?
Running around for it!?
What's wrong with that?
It's the treasure of treasures for me!
Don't you dare go makin' fun of Bura-Kura!
You're the one makin' fun of things!
You threw away your chance to get a job for a single autograph!
My, my, both of you, please calm down.
Well then, Kagami-sensei,
have you considered my offer?
I refuse!
Big brother!
I was a teacher for only one month,
but in that time, I realized the problem with it!
The problem?
By investing my precious time into less important things,
my anime blog fell from its first place ranking!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
It's impossible for this thing to become a proper teacher!
It looks like we're not making any progress here.
Seeing as we've got him bagged, let's get him to the school.
Are you sure you're fine with this?
Actually, before I invite Kagami-sensei to Hiiragi Academy,
I'm going to make him teach at
Icho Academy, our branch campus.
Huh?
Icho? You mean my school?
Keh! I already refused!
My blog is more important than your stupid school!
There it is.
That's Icho Academy.
Icho Academy
I've been awaiting your return, chairwoman.
And you...
Kagami Junichirou!
What's with this immediate hate I'm getting?
Would you give Kagami-sensei a tour around the school?
I refuse!
My...
It shouldn't be a surprise!
I've gone through the trouble of finding you
teachers to help improve this school,
so why are you always bringing back ones like this thing?
What's her deal?
You see,
not only is she captain of the kendo club, but she's also the
student council president and on the public morals committee
Momozono Makina-sama.
So that explains why she's being so rude to me.
She has immense influence and power.
People think of her as the chairwoman's right hand.
I've looked at the report.
You're an absolute NEET!
I'll never accept such a teacher!
But... the teachers you choose are always so boring, Makina-chan.
Boring!? I told you, the problem isn't whether they're interesting or not!
Right on the spot! Just what I'd expect from the student council president.
A person like me shouldn't be a teacher.
You see? Isn't he interesting?
He's just a hopeless guy who's too lazy to work!
O-Ouch...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry! Are you all right?
Huh?
She seems familiar...
You're still here?
Y-Yes, I'm sorry!
What's happened?
She was expelled from the school today.
She was working part-time.
She thought she would be fine
as long as the school didn't find out.
You reap what you sow.
Instantly expelled for working part-time.
Private schools are so strict.
Good grief.
Out of all the jobs you could have found, it was a maid café.
Just what were you thinking?
Hey!
You! What's the name?
I-It's Shikishima Kiriko.
Not that, the name of the café!
Ah, it's Akihabara's Heart-on-Heart.
Hey, Unusual Twintails over there,
expulsion is too severe of a punishment.
Revoke it.
Huh!? Y-You don't have the right to give orders to me like that!
And what's with that nickname!?
I have every right to, because...
from this moment onward, I'll be teaching at this academy.
Why work at a maid café, you ask?
You've just failed as a student
council president, Unusual Twintails!
Wh-What are you talking about?
My first lesson here will be just for you.
I'll teach you the prestige of a maid!
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
hibikasetai
I want it to resound,
kono koe o habatakasete
carry my voice,
sekaijuu ni furu na ai wo (aiou)
and fill the world with love
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell everyone that they can't stop dreamin'
shingou ga kawaru to sugu ni
As the signals change
hito no nami nagasaresou de
I get swept away in the crowd
kono machi wo aruku ni wa kitto
To walk the streets of this town
burenai kokoro hitsuyou
you need an unshakable heart
biru no sukima no kyuukutsu na sora ni
In that strip of sky between the city highrises
hikouki ga kirameita
I saw the sparkle of a plane fly by
watashi mo isoganakucha
I'd better get going, too
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
mou matenai
I just can't wait any more!
ooki na kaze maki okoshite
I'll raise a great wind
saidaifuusoku de ai wo (aiou)
and reach max speed so I can give you my love!
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell you that you can't stop dreamin'
Next Episode
Next Episode Search
SEARCH
My name is Momozono Makina.
It is not Unusual Twintails!
In the next episode...
I'm forced to work in a maid café for a day!
Mo-eh, Mohig...
There's no way I can say this!
Fourth lecture: Prestige of a Maid.
What does "maid of the maids" even mean?
Huh? She's the legendary cutter girl?