YD.
Do you know what it is?
Yukata Dating?
Yakiniku Desires?
Wrong!
You Do only what you want.
That's me, Kagami Junichirou!
Don't you think it's the best when you can have fun
while making others enjoy themselves too?
Hold it right there.
Being kicked out of school won't hurt me,
but losing my purpose in life most certainly will!
Watch her closely, because she's about to change reality!
I believe Kagami-sensei can truly show us
just how interesting Japan can be!
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true!
ichido no jinsei yaritai koto yaranakya
You only get one life so you gotta do the things you want
iza to nattara mucha shite omoshorikushite yarouze
So when it comes down to it, just shake things up and have some crazy fun
tsumaranai koto suru kimi ni wa oshioki ga hitsuyou kana?
But you never have any fun, do you need a little motivation?
seken no joushiki nanka wa kowashite
Set out to destroy society's preconceptions
kagami ni utsuru itsumono hyoujou kaeteyaruze
We'll swap that sour look for the one reflected in the mirror
soshite ichido suicchi iretara hoshii mono wa te ni irero
Once you flip your switch, your dreams will come within reach
hiiroo ga inakereba kimi ga hiiroo ni nareba ii to
"If there's no such thing as heroes, then you'll just have to become one."
sonna kotoba ga ikiru imi wo ataete kureta (donna shougai mo koete yuku)
Your words gave meaning to my life (I can overcome any obstacle)
kimaru no wa jibun nano
You choose the path you take
demo ne hitoribocchi ja nai kara
But that doesn't mean you need to walk it alone
monogatari no kotoba de ima sugu hontou no hiiroo ni nare!
Live up to the story you told me, become a true hero!
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true
kimi no ayumu jinsei orijinaru na sonzai sa
No matter what path you choose, it'll be your own original story
reberu agete tobidase mada mita koto no nai keshiki ga matsu
Level up and take to the skies, there's so much you've yet to see
kira kira to kagayakeru rejendo rea na bijon de egakareta
Like in your radiant vision of a sparkling legend
saikou no suteeji wo mezase!
you have to aim for the highest stage!
Good morning, big brother!
What are you up to?
I'm updating my anime blog with stuff I've been meaning to post, obviously.
There.
Now then...
Time to hit the hay.
Oh, could you close the curtains for me, please.
What was that?
Today's your first day teaching at my school, remember?
He is an Ultimate
Otaku Teacher
#05
SEARCH
Monster of  Icho Academy
Shikishima Kiriko's expulsion has been revoked,
and it has been decided that Kagami Junichirou is to be officially hired as a part-time lecturer at Icho Academy.
However,
his classroom and teaching schedule are still under careful consideration.
Do you have anything to add, student council president?
Chairwoman.
I am still against bringing this guy in as a teacher.
No matter how interested you are in him,
I will have nothing to do with supporting him.
If he gets himself into trouble here,
he will not receive any help from me.
Of course.
I would never expect such a thing from you.
Keep your distance from me now that we're here.
It would be really embarrassing if anyone finds out we're siblings.
S-Sensei!
Oh, French Fry!
Th-Thank you so much for yesterday.
It's all thanks to you that I can come back to school.
Is that so? That's great.
Why don't we have Cutter Girl's next gig at the school?
That's supposed to be a secret identity!
I don't want anyone at school to know about it!
Please keep all that underground stuff buried!
Are you sure?
Isn't that a lost cause?
That girl, she's definitely from yesterday's video!
Hey, look over there! It's the Cutter Girl!
Ah, what the—
What was that? An accident?
A footprint?
You were illegally parked.
Keep your car out of my way.
Did that guy send the car flying!?
He must be some sort of cyborg!
You're in my way too, huh?
S-Sensei, do something!
You want me to get myself killed?
A nerd shouldn't ever pick a fight these kind of characters—
Wanna know what happens when someone gets in my way?
Have a taste!
S-Sensei!
Sergeant Thunders' soul,
Revolver Cannon is missing!
Th-That's what you're worried about?
Damn it, where is it? Where did it go?
Well!? Help me search, Cyborg!
It's your fault the Revolver Cannon is missing!
Don't get in...
Sergeant Thunders can't transform without it!
my way!
Sensei!
Where is it!?
Nanami, you...
What were you about to do to my brother!?
I can't find it.
That guy is Suzune's big brother?
That weirdo?
Seriously!?
To think you have a older brother crawling on the ground for a doll's accessory.
I pity you, Kagami Suzune.
Sure, my big brother's a hopeless moron and an otaku,
but at least he's living a dignified life.
You just take your anger out on others to feel better about yourself!
He's a gazillion times better than a weakling like you!
You know, your bat's in my way.
You bet it is. So what?
That's enough.
Chairwoman!
It's the Chairwoman!
Oh, Lovely Options!
Could you ask everyone to help me look for Sergeant Thunders' Revolver Cannon?
Understood.
Listen up everyone.
I would like to introduce you to our school's newest teacher, Kagami Junichirou-sensei.
Sensei?
This weird dude?
Let me rephrase what he said earlier.
Yes, yes.
"I'm taking charge of this match."
"Before you can challenge my sister,
you'll be facing me, your homeroom teacher, first!"
...is what he said.
Yes, yes.
Wait, what!?
Interesting.
Hey, wait a minute...
The match shall be held in three days.
It will not end until one side admits defeat. No other rules shall be put in place.
As usual, I can never understand this woman's intentions...
I'm looking forward to our battle three days from now.
Hey! Why did you decide everything yourself!?
Chairwoman.
Were you serious when you called him a homeroom teacher?
Didn't you say that his placement would be chosen carefully?
Of course, and I gave it careful thought.
This was the perfect time to choose.
Liar!
I see...
Big brother, you should be put in charge of my class.
It might make things easier for you.
Huh? What do you mean by that?
My class is really small right now.
It used to be bigger, but Nanami sent a bunch of students to the hospital.
Big brother!?
Sensei!
Take him to the infirmary!
There it is, the Revolver Cannon...
I've got three days to live, huh?
Just like these crispy falling leaves.
I'll be crinkled and crunched!
God, could you be any more negative?
Cheer up, big brother.
I'll do something about Nanami.
Quit whining!
Hold on...
I have an idea.
I met a senpai online
who's really dependable in rough situations like this.
What I'd really like to know
is what kind of person this guy is.
I'm sure he looks like a character straight out of a fighting game.
Welcome home,
Oujo-sama!
Ah, Senpai!
Good grief, Kiri, I told you I don't live that kind of life anymore.
A girl?
Isn't it against the rules to discuss dangerous stuff like this?
That sounds a lot like...
What's wrong, big brother?
But Senpai, didn't you tell me before,
"Don't ever think that abiding by the rules
will guarantee your usefulness to society"?
Well, I guess you could say that phrase works for people like me,
but for you, it's at least ten years too early to live by.
U-UpperCute?
Upper?
Cute?
So the senpai you wanted to discuss this with
happens to be one of my brother's old students.
I was surprised too!
You said you'd take responsibility for what you did to me,
but then you left school out of nowhere!
Big brother?
Hey, UpperCute! Don't say it that way!
So Seijuurou is still up to no good, huh?
Wait, you've met Cyborg before?
Yeah.
He was my kohai back in middle school.
He started getting himself in trouble around the time I was at my worst, so I looked after him.
So Cyborg was sort of like your student!?
You're amazing!
Seijuurou's father was a famous professional baseball player.
Seijuurou had a gift for it as well,
so he spent his childhood playing it.
"Remove every obstacle that blocks
your path, and keep moving forward."
That's what his father believed, and that's what he was taught.
By the time Seijuurou made it to middle school,
he was already as skilled as a national level pitcher.
Strike!
But his father made a lot of enemies.
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Nanami sparks uproar
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
He felt lonely, and when he retired due to an accident,
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
Big mouth Nanami boasts away
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
The owner also had some sour words to share
"Hey, hey, hey! Didn't I tell you to cut the crap!?"
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
Big Mouth Quits Baseball
Refuses to change his behavior.
Shunned by his
teammates and friends.
Already "past his prime."
people fiercely bashed him.
He passed away from an illness later on,
harboring his despair to the end.
Ever since then, he's been a different person.
He injured his arm at one point,
but refused to leave the mound.
His teammates began to call him a monster.
But that wasn't out of praise or respect.
It was meant to isolate him, to alienate him.
And just like his father, Seijuurou started feeling lonely.
And then, in the finals of the prefectural competition,
a shallow fly ball, one even a grade schooler could catch, flew towards second base.
The second baseman was the ace of the team before Seijuurou.
Damn you!
After the incident, Seijuurou was banned from playing any baseball in middle school.
That's everything I know about him.
But how did a problem child like him make it into our elite school?
Oh, come to think of it, not only are problem
children accepted, the school's even hired one.
So it must have been the chairwoman?
It was one hundred percent her.
And now she's pitting her precious problem children against each other.
That girl, just what is she scheming?
Well, it looks like Cyborg is a pretty
interesting character, which is just what I like.
I guess I'll play along with Lovely Options.
I see.
You'll clear all my debts and will pay for all of my school expenses
so long as I attend your school.
This sounds like some kind of dream.
But my answer's no.
I can take care of myself.
Besides, I refuse to stand on the mound ever again.
You're misunderstanding things.
I am not here to recruit you for our baseball team.
Your duty is to attend my school for the next three years.
There is no way around it, since I've purchased you.
You have no choice in the matter.
Kagami Junichirou
Tomorrow
I'll be waiting for you
by the school gate
tomorrow at 10 o'clock
in the morning.
"I'll be waiting for you by the school gate tomorrow at 10 o'clock in the morning."
You got guts, calling me out like this.
K-Kanou-senpai?
Wh-Why are you here?
Seijuurou, you...
I have an idea for the match in two days.
I thought our fight had no rules—
There are no rules,
so we can decide ourselves how to settle things.
And I thought
we could do it with a game.
You want to settle this with a game?
If you're scared, you can refuse,
however...
I'll just have to leak all sorts of shameful pictures of your precious Kanou-senpai on the internet.
Wait, what was that!?
And the loser will be the winner's slave for the rest of his life.
You bastard, that's dirty!
That's just a huge boomerang, Cyborg.
I could say the same thing to you.
Forcing others into submission by doing what you do best.
Isn't that your usual method?
You make good use of violence.
Bring it on.
I'll have you crying like a baby two days from now.
Be prepared for that, Otaku Teacher!
This is certainly getting interesting.
What does he mean by shameful pictures?
Could they be those!?
Or maybe the ones from that other time!?
Bullshit!
This thing isn't working! How am I supposed to practice?
K-Kanou-senpai?
Here. I figured you would need a newer console to practice with.
Thanks.
I'll also be staying over tonight and
tomorrow to help you train for the match.
But there's no way I can ask that much from you—
If you give up this fight because
you're afraid of becoming a slave,
there's gonna be shameful
pictures of me all over the internet!
So I'm here to observe you.
"Observe"?
But he's a teacher, he wouldn't really—
He would.
There are things anyone else can do that he can't,
but there are things he can easily do that nobody else can, thanks to his YD.
He's the "You Do only what you want" person,
Kagami Junichirou.
That's the kind of guy he is!
YD?
That guy's supposed to be a teacher, right?
I hope Sensei will be okay.
Well, I'm sure he has a super secret plan right now.
No, I'm serious!
Then I'll take it seriously too!
It's fine, it's fine, go right ahead!
It's all right!
Wh-Why is Sensei with a girl?
My!
You know how we have a deal right now where you get a free drink for bringing in new masters?
Kagamin's always using it.
Free drinks?
You'll see!
In two days time, I'll be out there making the hottest plays anyone has ever seen!
Oh, will you?
Yeah, you bet!
Well, it's already clear who's gonna win—
What do you think you're doing, Sensei!
Oh, French Fry!
Nanami-kun and Senpai are training right now to beat you!
And yet...
And yet, you're sitting around here flirting with some girl!
I-I won't tolerate this!
Sensei, you...
Sensei, you... you should just explode!
What's her problem?
There we go!
Nice, you're finally getting better at it!
To play this game seriously, you need to
know the rules and formations of soccer.
You've gotten a lot better already.
You must be as smart as I thought.
If you're this smart, why are you still acting like an idiot?
What!? Sensei isn't home yet?
No way, he's not flirting with that girl is he?
Huh? What? Flirting with a girl?
I hope he explodes!
Huh? What?
Just what are you up to, big brother!?
Senpai, you've changed a lot.
I didn't recognize you at first.
You're wrong.
I haven't changed a bit.
I've just found a place where I belong.
Come on! Focus, focus!
Dad!
Hang in there, Dad!
Dad...
Seijuurou...
Remove every obstacle that blocks
your path, and keep moving forward.
That's what I've always taught you.
Yeah. That's why you can't lose to an illness!
However, that philosophy will leave you all alone.
And you'll come to regret your entire life.
Your arm which used to be as thick as a log, is now as slender as a tree branch now.
This isn't him. This isn't my dad.
Dad would...
never reject his philosophy.
My dad would never lose!
Wait up, bro...
What's up with you, bastard?
That's why, I...
He ain't answerin' us!
You hear me, thorn head!?
Quit spacin' out and apologize!
Don't you dare get in my way!
Unlike Senpai,
I don't belong anywhere.
All I know is that right now is that
that guy is in my way.
I absolutely will not lose.
I'm glad to see you didn't get cold feet.
Right back at you.
Though, you're looking pretty worn out.
I've been practicing without a
wink of sleep the past two days.
But I've still got one more game left in me for you.
I'm not so sure of that.
After all, we'll be playing a game of soccer.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
What?
Who said it would be a video game?
I only ever spoke of a game for this contest.
A soccer game.
You!
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
hibikasetai
I want it to resound,
kono koe o habatakasete
carry my voice,
sekaijuu ni furu na ai wo (aiou)
and fill the world with love
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell everyone that they can't stop dreamin'
shingou ga kawaru to sugu ni
As the signals change
hito no nami nagasaresou de
I get swept away in the crowd
kono machi wo aruku ni wa kitto
To walk the streets of this town
burenai kokoro hitsuyou
you need an unshakable heart
biru no sukima no kyuukutsu na sora ni
In that strip of sky between the city highrises
hikouki ga kirameita
I saw the sparkle of a plane fly by
watashi mo isoganakucha
I'd better get going, too
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
mou matenai
I just can't wait any more!
ooki na kaze maki okoshite
I'll raise a great wind
saidaifuusoku de ai wo (aiou)
and reach max speed so I can give you my love!
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell you that you can't stop dreamin'
Next Episode
SEARCH
I'm the cyborg, Nanami Seijuurou!
To maintain peace on Earth—
Hey, you!
Don't mess with me, Otaku Teacher!
In the next episode...
My team and Otaku Teacher's team battle in a rule-free soccer game.
The loser becomes a slave forever, you got that!?
Sixth Lecture: An Interesting View.
I'm no longer alone?
Huh, you don't know a thing about me!