YD.
Do you know what it is?
Yukata Dating?
Yakiniku Desires?
Wrong!
You Do only what you want.
That's me, Kagami Junichirou!
I happen to be Hiiragi Private Academy's board chairwoman,
Hiiragi Koyomi.
I am here to hire you.
The first mistake you made was thinking you could possibly outsmart me in Akiba.
Just give up already!
You there, Unusual Twintails,
expulsion is too severe of a punishment.
Revoke it.
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true!
ichido no jinsei yaritai koto yaranakya
You only get one life so you gotta do the things you want
iza to nattara mucha shite omoshorikushite yarouze
So when it comes down to it, just shake things up and have some crazy fun
tsumaranai koto suru kimi ni wa oshioki ga hitsuyou kana?
But you never have any fun, do you need a little motivation?
seken no joushiki nanka wa kowashite
Set out to destroy society's preconceptions
kagami ni utsuru itsumono hyoujou kaeteyaruze
We'll swap that sour look for the one reflected in the mirror
soshite ichido suicchi iretara hoshii mono wa te ni irero
Once you flip your switch, your dreams will come within reach
hiiroo ga inakereba kimi ga hiiroo ni nareba ii to
"If there's no such thing as heroes, then you'll just have to become one."
sonna kotoba ga ikiru imi wo ataete kureta (donna shougai mo koete yuku)
Your words gave meaning to my life (I can overcome any obstacle)
kimaru no wa jibun nano
You choose the path you take
demo ne hitoribocchi ja nai kara
But that doesn't mean you need to walk it alone
monogatari no kotoba de ima sugu hontou no hiiroo ni nare!
Live up to the story you told me, become a true hero!
yume wo kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true
kimi no ayumu jinsei orijinaru na sonzai sa
No matter what path you choose, it'll be your own original story
reberu agete tobidase mada mita koto no nai keshiki ga matsu
Level up and take to the skies, there's so much you've yet to see
kira kira to kagayakeru rejendo rea na bijon de egakareta
Like in your radiant vision of a sparkling legend
saikou no suteeji wo mezase!
you have to aim for the highest stage!
He is an Ultimate
Otaku Teacher
#04
SEARCH
Prestige of a Maid
The prestige of a maid?
That's right.
If you don't understand it,
then you have no right to expel her.
Jobs as maidservants began to
appear around the 19th century.
It was a symbol of wealth to own one during the Victorian Era of the British Empire.
There were 17 different types,
such as housemaids or step girls.
The "maids" you see in maid cafés are fakes by comparison.
How pathetic.
I knew it.
You're absolutely clueless.
Wh-What do you mean by that!?
Explain yourself!
Are you sure?
Asking me to teach you something
is the same as admitting that I am a teacher.
Our school's principles are built on learning,
understanding, and developing one's own answers.
It allows students to build confidence and hone their minds.
The prestige of a maid?
Understanding something like that is pointless.
There is no way working at some café full of fakes aligns with our school's principles!
Are you certain?
So certain that you would swear by those words,
Makina-chan?
But I mean, it's...
Completely certain?
Well,
there you have it.
imou tos 4 lyfe
Heart  on  Heart
Welcome home, Goshujin-sama, Oujo-sama.
Why am I...
Well, I'll be right back then.
Kagamin!
Thanks for coming again!
Hey, manager!
This girl is the manager!?
Hold it, big brother!
You've been here before?
Maybe once or twice...
Kagamin holds the top record of
coming home fifty times a month.
He's our most esteemed Platinum Member!
In fact, he was here this morning too.
Oh, so this is where you've been blowin' all your cash!?
W-Well, this café is school-themed,
so I thought it'd help get me in the mindset...
More damned lies!
They get along so well.
Heart
on
Anyway, back on topic...
This is the manager of this school-themed maid café, Heart on Heart.
She may be small, but she has studied maids
abroad in England. She was also my classmate—
Hi! I'm Minami Kitayama, 17 years old!
17 years old!
Uh... Anyway, manager,
I need to ask for a favor.
What?
Would you let Unusual Twintails work here for the day?
Huh? Why me!?
Unless you experience it yourself,
there's no way you would ever
understand a maid's prestige, right?
If you don't want to do it alone, my sister will join you.
Come again!?
No problems then, right?
Th-This is absurd...
Chairwoman, would you please say something...
Goshujin-samas and Oujo-samas who have returned today, here is our school's announcement.
Two new maids are entering our school today.
Makki-chan and Suzu-chan!
If you knew she hated maids,
why didn't you say anything?
I'm quite fond of that expression she's making now, you see.
Oh...
I see...
Th-Thank you for waiting,
G-Goshujin-sama...
Here are your Golden French Fry.
Please enjoy!
Hold up, Makki.
These fries are missing something.
You forgot to cast the Deliciousness Spell!
S-Spell?
Look. Watch your senpai.
It's her!
Become delicious!
Moe-moe-kyun!
I knew it. She's...
Y-You want me to do that!?
Me? Right here!?
Hey, where's my spell?
Hurry it up!
I can't do this!
You're not as tough as I thought, Unusual Twintails.
Those fries...
I had Kiriko cast her spell on them.
She did amazing!
I should start calling her French Fry.
But that nonsense has nothing to do with maids.
Moe-moe-kyun!
It's still meaningless...
Well, suit yourself.
But doesn't it bother you that you're expelling someone who can do something you can't?
How dull.
Your character is so boring.
Lovely Options has her nice little quirks,
but with someone like you at her side,
I'd say her plan's only a 1-cour at most.
Stop right there!
I was only taking a break.
Don't underestimate Momozono Makina!
I'm going back to work.
Oh, now she's fired up.
Moving along...
It's time...
to start the next lesson.
Please come again!
Until next time!
There's no need to be so nervous.
As long as it pleases your master, anything's fine.
There aren't any hard-and-fast rules here.
A-Apologies for the wait.
Wow!
Isn't that great, Takeshi?
She gave you got a rice omelette, your favorite!
Yeah!
J-Just a moment, Goshujin-sama...
Takeshi-kun
Wow!
Thank you!
You're welcome.
It looks so cool!
Eating it would be such a waste!
Please enjoy, Goshujin-sama.
Hey now, don't tell me you actually think you've got this all down already.
O-Of course not...
Writing names on omelettes is only the basics of the basics.
Even my sister can do it.
Look over there!
There, it's finished, Goshujin-sama!
It's a work of art!
And that's not all.
Each and every master has their own individual tastes.
You need to take your time and carefully learn what each one wants
in order to truly understand them.
Wh-What are you...
For example, look over there.
U-Um... I'd like an orange juice.
Huh? Orange?
Well, it doesn't have to be that...
Here ya' go.
U-Um, could I get a glass?
Huh? Right, here.
Uh... How am I supposed to use this?
You sure are bossy...
Here!
Uh... T-Thank you.
That's horrible service!
Not quite. Take another look.
Huh?
Doesn't he look happy?
She can't help it...
That's right.
The manager instantly recognized what her master desired
and tailored her service to that.
U-Uh, excuse me, could you also cast a spell?
Oh yeah, so sorry. Totally forgot.
Taste better. 'Kay, spell's over.
Oh, she's treating me so badly.
But it makes me kind of happy...
That's the work of an expert.
Maybe she'll ignore them,
I'm so sorry!
or maybe she'll act like a klutz.
And sometimes, despite her age,
she will even be their little sister.
I'm so happy!
She understands their desires and adjusts her character accordingly.
Maids are profound, aren't they?
How close do you think you can get to her level, Unusual Twintails?
Didn't I tell you? Don't underestimate me.
I'm going to give it my best till the very end.
Yeah, you did.
Moe-moe-kyun!
No way, you came back again?
Please come again,
Goshujin-sama!
How'd you like your busy first day of work?
Now do you understand a maid's prestige, Unusual Twintails?
I guess...
They use creativity and imagination to read their masters' feelings
Become delicious! Kyun-kyun!
and they follow their own rules to put them to ease.
Sorry for your wait, Goshujin-sama!
Is that right?
50 out of 100.
And you know what the other half is already.
If I remember correctly, the Icho Academy principles were
"built on learning, understanding,
and developing one's own answers,
leading students to confidence and honing their minds," right?
That's right...
Then why would you expel French Fry?
Don't tell me it's because she broke school rules.
You're like some background character spewing generic lines.
Shut up!
Even if I told you you're right,
that doesn't change what maid cafés are.
The reality is that society will never understand them beyond that level.
It is my duty to preserve our school's reputation and enforce the rules.
She must be punished!
The decision has already been made!
Interesting, I like where this is going.
Looks like the lesson's not over yet.
Part A ends here.
We'll settle this in Part B!
Hey,
did you see that tweet?
Yeah, I saw it!
Something happening at 9pm today, Izuzu Building!
[OFFICIAL] Kaiketsu Battle Royale
OK!! is everyone ready!?
It's at 9pm tonight, right?
Really? Guess I'll check it out.
Oh, wanna go?
Why not.
Let's check it out!
Something interesting
is apparently happening
It's around here, right?
I wonder what's up.
is apparently happening
Who tweeted that, anyway?
P-Part B?
Yeah, that's right.
Unusual Twintails, you told me you
understood the good qualities of a maid,
but because society happens to look down on them
you have no choice but to expel French Fry to protect the school's reputation, correct?
If that's the case, then all we need to do is change society's views...
using her!
Huh? What!?
What are you talking about!?
Just watch, Unusual Twintails.
All right,
it's your time to sing.
Wow!
That tweet sure spread fast.
Just check out this crowd!
Wh-What's going on!?
All we need from you is the perfect performance,
and society's views will be changed overnight.
That's the Part B!? Are you insane!?
That's impossible. There's no way I can do that...
Of course you can.
After all, you're the maidest of maids
the legendary underground idol...
Cutter Girl, right?
You used to show up on NukoDouni
anonymously, in a maid outfit.
Your moves were so sharp that people began to call you Cutter Girl, the girl in the maid outfit.
When I met you at the school gates,
I knew I recognized you from somewhere.
I love those legs
Shake those hips!!
She's sooo good........
However, you've never shown your face online.
But as I watched you work, I figured out who you were.
I'm sorry! I...
Stop, Shikishima-san!
Is what he just said true?
That you're an underground idol?
Why would you do something like that?
I've... loved maids ever since I was little,
because I thought their outfits were really cute.
That's why I started working here.
At first, I sang and I danced as part of the job,
but then I found myself genuinely enjoying performing.
I began to do it in private, separate from work.
I'm sorry.
I told you a maid's job is to make her masters happy,
but I did it all for myself instead!
I'm no "maidest of maids" like Sensei said,
I'm just a failure!
Just a selfish girl!
Then how do you explain this?
That's...
Hey, Unusual Twintails,
here's your other 50 points.
The Best
Thank You
Breathtaking
Squeeee
Nice
Awesome!!
I'll come back
Wow
Thanks
Will you stand by your words even after seeing these photos?
Hey, French Fry, don't you think being able to enjoy others' happiness
is the best part of the job?
That's something you can be proud of.
You're a star role model for every maid in Akiba,
and I've set the perfect stage for you,
so give your masters around the world a show to remember!
Hold it right there.
Stop it.
If you choose not to do this,
I'm willing to reconsider your punishment.
But if you walk out there and sing
you'll lose any chance of ever coming back.
Your singing won't bring about any of the changes he says it will!
Nothing will change!
You'll only be making a fool of yourself!
Don't let that NEET ruin your life!
Don't believe what he says!
You know, I've realized...
Being kicked out of school won't hurt me,
but losing my purpose in life most certainly will!
Unusual Twintails,
watch her closely, because she's about to change reality!
Come on already...
I'm used to waiting, but this is pretty boring.
It should be soon.
Wait! Hey, what's that?
There's a girl there!
Seriously!?
I'm at your service, Goshujin-sama!
Heading home through Akiba
you make a stop in front of Heart on Heart.
I want to see your happy face,
that shining smile.
We'll write your name on a rice omelet with ketchup,
we're Heart on Heart.
When you tell me that you've fallen crazy in love with me
it makes my heart flutter
and it makes me so happy I dance.
I'm at my limit! Ke-Ke-Pe!
Nothing exceeds our love for our masters.
Now I'll cast my spell for you.
Dude, her moves are crazy sharp!
Become delicious!
And the video's amazing too!
Moe-moe-kyun!
How did they manage to sync all the screens on all the buildings!?
That's magic only a maid can do!
Record her! How often do you see something like this!?
I'll always serve you.
Hey, what should I name the video?
You're always number one.
Jeez, man, you don't know?
As long as you're here, you'll have fun.
That's the legendary maidest of maids, Cutter Girl!
We'll make sure our masters are pleased.
Awesome!
That's the prestige, that's right, that's the prestige of a maid.
Makina-chan.
A video stream of this has already amassed ten million views globally.
Ten million...
If you were to expel her now,
I believe it would damage our school's reputation.
Nothing exceeds our love for our masters,
Why?
Why are you taking her side, Chairwoman?
so now I'll cast my spell for you.
You're mistaken.
Become delicious!
I simply side with interesting students.
Moe-moe-kyun!
Kagami-sensei helped bring out her interesting personality.
That's magic only a maid can do!
I'll always serve you.
I believe he can truly show us...
You're always number one.
As long as you're here, you'll have fun.
just how interesting Japan can be!
We'll make sure our masters are pleased.
That's the prestige, that's right, that's the prestige of a maid!
That's the end of today's lesson!
Thank you!
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
hibikasetai
I want it to resound,
kono koe o habatakasete
carry my voice,
sekaijuu ni furu na ai wo (aiou)
and fill the world with love
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell everyone that they can't stop dreamin'
shingou ga kawaru to sugu ni
As the signals change
hito no nami nagasaresou de
I get swept away in the crowd
kono machi wo aruku ni wa kitto
To walk the streets of this town
burenai kokoro hitsuyou
you need an unshakable heart
biru no sukima no kyuukutsu na sora ni
In that strip of sky between the city highrises
hikouki ga kirameita
I saw the sparkle of a plane fly by
watashi mo isoganakucha
I'd better get going, too
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
mou matenai
I just can't wait any more!
ooki na kaze maki okoshite
I'll raise a great wind
saidaifuusoku de ai wo (aiou)
and reach max speed so I can give you my love!
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell you that you can't stop dreamin'
Next Episode
SEARCH
This is Shikishima Kiriko, also known as French Fry!
I had so much fun singing my heart out to the crowd, Goshujin-sama!
In the next episode...
the baddest kid in our school,
Nanami Seijuro, goes on a rampage!
Kagami-sensei has to face off with him!
Fifth lecture: The Monster of Icho Academy.
I'm glad to have a reliable senpai for times like this!
Huh? Senpai, you're Kagami-sensei's student?