Heck yeah! I'm in first place!
So noisy!
Do you have any idea what time it is, you moron!?
"My Super Dreadnought Story"
is now the highest rated anime blog!
If you got time for your stupid otaku blog,
then you have time to...
get a friggin' job!
Little sister, your brother has a disease called YD that prevents him from doing any work.
YD?
Yes, YD is...
a horrible disease in which
You Do only what you want—
Hey! Watch it!
I don't know what I would've done if a part of my collection was damaged.
Here!
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Starting tomorrow, you're going to be a teacher.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
Appointment Confirmation
Subject: Physics Teaching Position
Mr. Kagami Junichirou,
We are pleased to inform you that your application for the part-time physics teacher position
at Higashi Shinmei High School has been accepted.
A teacher, huh?
I know that a teaching job, even a part-time one,
could be invaluable for me right now.
And if they like my work,
I could even be promoted to full-time.
Not to mention they might go lightly on me since I graduated high school there.
So you'll—
Still, I cannot!
Because of my YD, you know?
I'm gonna wipe that smug look
right off your face!
Stop it!
Stupid big brother!
yume o kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true!
ichido no jinsei yaritai koto yaranakya
You only get one life so you gotta do the things you want
iza to nattara mucha shite omoshirokushite yarouze
So when it comes down to it, just shake things up and have some crazy fun
tsumaranai koto suru kimi ni wa oshioki ga hitsuyou kana?
But you never have any fun, do you need a little motivation?
seken no joushiki nanka wa kowashite
Set out to destroy society's preconceptions
kagami ni utsuru itsumono hyoujou kaeteyaruze
We'll swap that sour look for the one reflected in the mirror
soshite ichido suicchi iretara hoshii mono wa te ni irero
Once you flip your switch, your dreams will come within reach
hiiroo ga inakereba kimi ga hiiroo ni nareba ii to
"If there's no such thing as heroes, then you'll just have to become one."
sonna kotoba ga ikiru imi wo ataete kureta (donna shougai mo koete yuku)
Your words gave meaning to my life (I can overcome any obstacle)
kimeru no wa jibun nano
You choose the path you take
demo ne hitoribocchi ja nai kara
But that doesn't mean you need to walk it alone
monogatari no kotoba de ima sugu hontou no hiiroo ni nare!
Live up to the story you told me, become a true hero!
yume o kanaete jibun no mirai wo sono te ni tsukame
Take hold of your future and you can make your dreams come true
kimi no ayumu jinsei | orijinaru na sonzai sa
No matter what path you choose, it'll be your own original story
reberu agete tobidase mada mita koto no nai keshiki ga matsu
Level up and take to the skies, there's so much you've yet to see
kirakira to kagayakeru rejendo rea na bijon de egakareta
Like in your radiant vision of a sparkling legend
saikou no suteeji wo mezase!
you have to aim for the highest stage!
He is an Ultimate
Otaku Teacher
#01
SEARCH
I am a High School Teacher Now
Principal's Office
Ah, you really saved us!
Watanabe-sensei had to take her
maternity leave earlier than expected.
You'll look much better wearing that.
So take it seriously, like you used to.
Like I used to?
Excuse me... Sensei?
Sensei?
I'm finding it a bit hard to believe that you'd
hire a NEET without even an interview first.
In fact, I would've preferred to be rejected.
You don't have to be so modest!
You are the young genius Kagami Junichirou,
whose works were featured in the magazines
Nature and Science at the age of 17, aren't you?
After finishing university, you rejected research opportunities from institutes around the world.
What exactly have you been up to for over a year?
Writing, mostly. For my anime blog.
Huh? Why would you do that?
Because I've lost all my interest in science and physics.
nerai sadamete utsu no faiyaa
Take aim and fire
yume miru tsuu hando
your dreams with both hands!
This song... It's Magical Girl Bura-Kura's
opening theme, "Dream with Both Hands"!
U-Um... Excuse me? Sensei?
It's coming from the roof?
Hey, Sensei, wait!
I wasn't done—
You imbecile! It's a ninety second song.
It'll be over before you finish blabbering!
Imbecile?
onnanoko dakedo hiiroo
Not just a girl but also a hero.
hiroin janai hiiroo
Not your everyday heroine, a true hero!
koi mo batoru mo hitorigachi
Always the winner in both love and war.
bakyun zukyun yume wo nosete
Bang! Boom! Gotta aim with your heart!
bakyun zukyun hyappatsu hyakuchuu
Bang! Boom! Never miss your mark!
ai no sorujaa
A soldier of love,
mahou shoujo bura-kura
Magical Girl Bura-Kura!
Who's there!?
Wow! You're so good! Just like the real thing!
I'm going to be a voice actress.
A voice actress?
I was singing out here to train
my voice and test my courage.
Surprised?
I'm already attending a training school.
You're talking to a future sta—
Are you saying...
it's easy to become a voice actress!?
There are over a thousand voice acting schools in Japan!
Tens of thousands graduate from those schools each year,
and less than a hundred ever
manage to make a living off of it!
Only one out of every hundred thousand ever becomes a star!
You're more likely to get run over on the street in the next three days!
Voice actresses are goddesses!
Having a pretty voice alone
isn't enough to become one!
So you can say you want to be a voice actress,
but as far as I can tell, it's not your choice to make—
I'll be the one to decide that!
She's the kind of person who would sock a guy she's just met?
I'm not good with those types.
I wonder what our new physics teacher is like.
I heard he's some genius who used to go to our school.
He apparently got a Nobel Prize for his research before he even graduated.
Minako!
You're still singing those manga songs of yours up on the roof?
You're a third year now, grow up.
Why don't you toss this thing and hang out with us instead?
You know, like we used to.
Yo...
I-It's that guy?
Well, Watanabe-sensei's... well, uh...
Hold on, is that our new teacher?
on maternity leave... and, uh...
He looks like he's about to drop.
Is this guy really a genius?
I'm just not feeling it, but I've got to start the lesson somehow.
How do I...
How do I get out of this?
That's right!
From this day forth, I will be your physics teacher,
Kagami Junichirou!
This address will take you to an
increasingly popular smartphone game.
Rather than awful self introductions, we'll play this game instead!
And anyone skilled enough to beat me will get full marks on next week's quiz!
Kaiketsu
Battle Royale
Now, connect to the game and give me all you've got!
Party games are no different than life.
The students' play styles reflect their real personality.
It's the perfect way to get to know them.
Agh!
What's wrong?
I lost again!
Kitou Miho. So she's the class leader type, huh?
You're so bad!
UpperCute?
So she's in this class, huh?
Honestly, this class is an open book.
Oh, UpperCute!
You eat your lunch up here too?
UpperCu—
Hold on! You can't just give people weird nicknames!
I'll find somewhere else to eat!
Oh, that's right.
So, why are you being bullied?
I know Kitou Miho and her posse are the main perpetrators,
but everyone else is avoiding you as well to stay out of the fray.
You had the guts to punch me in the face,
so why aren't you fighting back against them?
You're a weird one.
Weird?
You're the last one I want to hear that from!
Everyone's been wondering,
"If he's so incredible, why didn't he go on to become a researcher?"
There's nothing weird about it.
All I wanted to do was build an Anywhere Door.
Anywhere Door?
Building one of those is impossible—
I made one.
Or rather, I came up with a theory
that proves it's possible to build one.
I submitted it to a scientific magazine for peer review,
but it just caused a whole lot of confusion.
However, I managed to finish the
theoretical blueprints while I was in university.
Unfortunately, due to technological limitations and the time it would require,
it'll be the 22nd century before we find out.
But it sure was fun.
So that's why you won't do research any more?
I didn't study physics and science to master them.
I just suffer from YD!
YD?
It's a disease where You Do only what you want.
Then what's wrong with me becoming a voice actress!?
Voice actresses are special!
They are goddesses who breathe life into a character!
I don't fight back against what Miho and the others do to me...
because I'm going to be a hero.
This is just a trial to becoming one.
Huh? Weren't you going to be a voice actress?
If I can be a voice actress, then I'll be a hero as well!
A high school girl with an
ambition to become a hero...
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Shinmei Highschool Branch Website
Login
Please enter your credentials
Jeez, that lesson kept me so late.
Someone is following me.
I have to run away.
Hey, hey, you'll let me do what I want for 5,000 yen, right?
S-Sensei?
Just run!
My power level is only one!
So you were the one following me?
You see,
I found something on this website...
The Shinmei High School Branch Website,
our school's underground social network.
What... is this?
Kitou Miho created a profile for you, and posted it on the website.
So, it got me a little worried.
Then, the reason you followed me was...
Well, you were just unlucky that
some idiot took the site seriously.
I can't blame him for believing it, though.
If you look at my past, it shows.
My family life was really stressful back then.
Watching them bothered me,
so I hung out with Miho and the others instead.
We spent our nights fighting and fooling around, wasting time.
And then one day...
This world is shit.
There's no point in living in a world like this.
I'd rather just die.
Life isn't like a manga or anime,
where heroes save you in a time of need.
Here's some advice for you, Rabbit.
If there's no such thing as heroes,
then you'll just have to become one.
Those words gave my life a meaning.
Later on, I found out that
Sergeant Thunders said those words,
in the anime Magical Girl Bura-Kura.
But at that moment I realized
that even words from a fantasy story could save a person.
If I can become a voice actress, then I can truly be a hero!
That's why I'm ready to face every obstacle that gets in my way.
If I can't do that, I'll never
become the hero I want to be!
A hero, huh?
Hey, haven't you noticed
everyone staring at you lately?
You can thank us when you become a star
considering all we've done to spread the word about you.
By the way, we heard voice actresses need to take good care of their throats,
so we made juice that will do wonders for your voice.
I heard Miho and her posse made her drink something full of chalk dust.
That's why she's in the nurse's office now? They went too far!
Nurse's Office
UpperCute!
Sensei...
I must have drank some juice that went bad.
Your voice...
This way, I have the chance to level up again.
I'll be able to voice a wider range of characters now.
Miho's posse did this to you, right?
Please stay out of this.
This is my past I'm fighting here.
It should be my strength that overcomes it.
After all, heroes are supposed to work alone, right?
I see...
You need more practice staying in character,
UpperCute.
Nobody's here.
Damn, I'm crazy tired.
What does he want, anyway?
Hey there, Wicked Blonde!
Who are you calling wicked!?
What's your deal, calling us out here?
So, is bullying Minako really that much fun to you?
What could you possibly be talking about?
I haven't the faintest idea.
Perfect. That's just the answer I wanted to hear to make things interesting.
About five percent as interesting of the late night shows on TV Yomi.
Sorry to bother you all...
Now, let the lesson begin.
So, what are we going to do?
Kagami is totally on to us.
Could he have hacked the branch site?
Huh? I don't know who made it,
but the website's security is top notch.
It's not something you can just hack into.
That's true. Not even an otaku like him could possibly...
New Message from Miho-san
What?
Miho, did you send me mail?
Huh? I didn't.
But look at this!
It came from your branch site address.
What's it say?
Sender: Miho
To: Yo-Ko
Subject: no subject
Look up
Look up?
What is this!?
Chalk dust!?
You bullies that prey on helpless girls!
I, Justice Man,
shall teach you a lesson!
Justice Man? You're just Kagami!
Your clothes and voice make it obvious!
Eh? Why can we see ourselves on this?
Currently, this video,
titled "Justice Man Punishes The Mean High School Girls,"
is being broadcast to the whole world!
What!?
Oh! There's already three
different comment threads up.
You! How can you call yourself a teacher when you're doing this without any evidence?
Evidence?
You three are always chatting away on the Shinmei High School Branch Website.
Don't tell me, you managed to hack it?
Hacking?
Why would I bother with that?
After all, the creator of that website...
is me.
When I was in school,
I set up that website with other otaku in my class to exchange photos.
After I graduated, I took my eyes off it to focus on other things,
but you've already managed to mess it up.
I hope you're ready for your punishment, baby monkeys.
Which means he can pull up all of our chat logs.
For your punishment, I'm going to post your personal information from the site
into this comment thread for the video.
Stop it, this isn't a joke!
Our home addresses and phone numbers are in there!
We were only bothering her because
she quit hanging out with us out of nowhere.
We weren't bullying her!
You're right. It wasn't really bullying...
Right?
Criminal Law, chapter 204, causing physical injury!
Criminal Law, chapter 222, intimidation!
Criminal Law, chapter 61, section 1, assault instigation!
What you girls were doing was a legitimate criminal act.
Please, stop this...
I'm just helping you become famous.
From this day on, everyone will be watching you...
for the rest of your lives.
No way!
Oh, have the prank calls begun already?
I suggest you answer it before they call your house or the school instead.
H-Hello?
Just kidding!
Were you scared?
Everything up until now has
been a prank of my creation,
even the threads and comments.
Do you understand what it feels like to be on the receiving end now?
Sensei!
Oh, UpperCute.
What did you do?
Nothing much. I was just giving my poorly behaved students a few extra lessons.
Didn't I tell you I would handle this myself?
Why did you do this yourself?
If there's no such thing as heroes,
then you'll just have to become one.
But even the person who said that,
Sergeant Thunders of Bura-Kura,
had her life saved many times by Lance Corporal Hartman, right?
Even Batman has Robin to back him up.
Heroes may live a lonely life, but that
doesn't mean they have to fight alone as well.
Rabbit.
I told you, I have YD.
You Do only what you want.
That's the end of today's lesson.
Sensei... it was you...
He knew everything about me from the start...
Thank you, Sensei!
Interesting.
He's very interesting, indeed...
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
hibikasetai
I want it to resound,
kono koe o habatakasete
carry my voice,
sekaijuu ni furu na ai wo (aiou)
and fill the world with love
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell everyone that they can't stop dreamin'
shingou ga kawaru to sugu ni
As the signals change
hito no nami nagasaresou de
I get swept away in the crowd
kono machi wo aruku ni wa kitto
To walk the streets of this town
burenai kokoro hitsuyou
you need an unshakable heart
biru no sukima no kyuukutsu na sora ni
In that strip of sky between the city highrises
hikouki ga kirameita
I saw the sparkle of a plane fly by
watashi mo isoganakucha
I'd better get going, too
sou
Day by day, that's right, step by step
mou matenai
I just can't wait any more!
ooki na kaze maki okoshite
I'll raise a great wind
saidaifuusoku de ai wo (aiou)
and reach max speed so I can give you my love!
ima koko kara tsutaetai yo
I want to tell you that you can't stop dreamin'
Next Episode
SEARCH
Hey, this is UpperCute, Kanou Minako!
I would have never guessed that those posts were by Kagami-sensei.
In the end, he saved me twice.
Next episode, our YD teacher, Kagami Junichirou, makes the class representative lose her temper?
What are you going to do, Sensei?
Eh? Sensei harassed a woman?
Chapter two, Laws of Society.
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
Manga investigation blog
Super dreadnought story DX
Montana's late night anime
If it's true, he'll get more than just an uppercut to the face!
By the way, who was that woman at the end?